I'm very pleased to announce the new
partnership between Westwood One
America's largest audio network and the
Jordan B Peterson podcast with the
premiere episode released this Sunday
March 24th subsequent podcasts will be
released every Sunday
featuring lectures about issues of
profound psychological and social
importance and discussions with leading
scientists philosophers and authors I'm
also very happy that I will be joined in
this revised podcast by my daughter
Mikaela Petersen who will serve as
co-host and discussant it's a project we
have both been excited to develop and
are looking forward to continually
improving we hope that the Westwood one
partnership will improve the quality of
our production and introduced many new
listeners to the podcast